

Luis Gerardo Gomez Romero

FRONTEND WEB DEVELOPER

CONTACT

gerardogomezromero175@gmai

MY LINKS

GeraOSF

in geraosf

@ geraosf.github.io

Introduction

I'm Gerardo Gomez, a Front-end Web Developer with experience developing software solutions in the current company I'm working in, but also doing projects for clients as a freelancer.

My skills



Adaptability to change



Proactivity



Team player

Technologies and tools

I MASTER

React / JavaScript / HTML / CSS / Python / C / SQL / TypeScript / Jest / Tailwind / WordPress

Languages

Spanish

NATIVE/BILINGUAL

English

FLUID

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE/CAREER

THIRDROCK SYSTEMS

ThirdRock Systems

Frontend Web Developer
 Oct 2022 — TODAY

Working with a team as a frontend web developer for the Canadian company ThirdRock Systems.

TECHNOLOGIES AND TOOLS

JavaScript / HTML / CSS / WordPress



Upwork

Freelance Web Developer

Sep 2022 — TODAY (1 month)

Developing software solutions for clients all around the world in the freelance site Upwork.

TECHNOLOGIES AND TOOLS

JavaScript / React / HTML / CSS / TypeScript / Jest / Tailwind



LYPSA

Electronic diagnostic and repair technician

Sep 2020 — Feb 2021 (5 months)

Diagnose and repair faulty circuits from a telecommunications company called Izzi



Voxcentrix

Bilingual Customer Service Representative

Jun 2018 — Aug 2018 (2 months)

Car insurance agents for clients in the United States.

EDUCATION/**DEGREES**

Degrees



Instituto Tecnológico de Tijuana

Electrical Engineer

Aug 2015 — Jun 2022 (6 yrs. and 10 months)

Currently working on my final project in Electrical engineer specializing in automation.

TECHNOLOGIES AND TOOLS

Python / C / C++ / Matlab

Courses & Self Training

Oracle Next Education - Full stack development, Alura Latam

Apr 2022 — TODAY (6 months)

Learn React, Scrimba

Jul 2022 — Aug 2022 (1 month)

— CS50: Introduction to Computer Science, Harvard University

Jan 2022 — May 2022 (4 months)

— JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures, FreeCodeCamp

Nov 2021 — Feb 2022 (3 months)

Certificates



JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures Certification

Issued by: FreeCodeCamp

Feb 2022 — TODAY (8 months)



Mechanical Design at the level of Associate

Issued by: Dassault Systèmes

May 2021 — TODAY (1 year and 5 months)



e-Series Core Track - Robotic Arm Programming

Issued by: Universal Robots A/S
Oct 2020 — TODAY (2 yrs.)